// import { UserRole } from "~/src/models";
const UserRole = {
    ADMIN:'ADMIN',
    SUPER_ADMIN:'SUPER_ADMIN'
}
export const serverPort = 9088;

export const helpCenterId = 7;
export const currencyIntroductionId = 3;
export const affiliateChannel = 14;
export const convertFaqs = 73;
export const nonHelpcenterChannel = 85;
export const inviteChannel = 4;
export const financialChannel = 68;
export const chatChannel = 106;
export const strategyBotChannel = 108;

export const webFooterArticle = 17;
export const bitnasdaqLite = 123;
export const newsChannelId = 69;
export const flashNewsChannelId = 70;
export const bitnasdaqNewsChannelId = 70;
export const bitnasdaqPostChannelId = 90;
export const blogChannelId = 105;
export const p2pFaqChannel = 77;
export const promotionChannelId = 87;
export const announcementId = 16;
export const SubAnnouncementId = 86;

export const p2pSubchannelId = 80;
export const singlePageArticleId = 23;
export const recommendFriendChannel = 109;
export const rewardHubChannel = 100;
export const homeBannerChannelId = 2;
export const vipBannerChannelId = 114;
export const bnqUserGuide = 113;
export const chatBotId = "660b98e14b3c44c0160cf77b";

export const btcCtid = "1575964013659730564";
export const btcStrategyBot = "5348811875249548880";
export const termId = 20;
export const PrivacyPolicyId = 105;
export const termofserviceId = 167;
export const marginId = 61;
export const spotId = 60;
export const futureChannelId = 82;
export const userGuide = 92;
export const spotLimitMarketId = 60;
export const commonProblemsChannelId = 15;

//playcard
export const playcardFaqsMainChannelId = 116;
export const playcardFaqsSubChannelId = 116;
export const playcardTermsMainChannelId = 117;
export const playcardTermsSubChannelId = 117;
export const copyTradeChannelId = 118;
export const copyTradeUserGuide = 120;
export const copyTradeFaqs = 120;
export const amplifyAdminUids = [
    {
        uid: "20417362623",
        role: UserRole.ADMIN,
    },
    {
        uid: "126152719136",
        role: UserRole.SUPER_ADMIN,
    },
];
export const api = {
    channel: 19,
    subTitle: "api",
};

export const liveLink = "https://www.bitnasdaq.com";
export const copyTradeInviteLink = `${liveLink}/copy-trade/trader-user-center`;
export const playCardLink = `${liveLink}/play-card-game`;
export const btchHalvingDate = "2024-04-20T06:05:00";
export const privacysubtitle = "privacypolicy";
export const userAgrement = "useragreement";
export const cookiepolicy = "cookiepolicy";
export const termofservicess = "TermsofService";
export const privacypolicy = "privacypolicy";
export const invitationLink = "https://www.bitnasdaq.com/invite";
export const icoLink = "https://ico.bitnasdaq.com";
export const playcardImageLink = "https://images.bitnasdaq.io/playcard";
export const hashRulesLink = "https://theasciicode.com.ar";
export const hashDetailLink = "https://www.blockchain.com/explorer/blocks/eth"; //hashid

export const whitePaperLink = "https://images.bitnasdaq.com/WhitePaper-bnq.pdf";
export const appleStoreLink =
    "https://apps.apple.com/us/app/bitnasdaq-buy-sell-crypto/id6452725712";
export const appleStoreBetaLink = "https://testflight.apple.com/join/wr82YLnR";
export const googleLinkLink =
    "https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.bitnasdaq.exchange";
export const googleAuthenticator =
    "https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.apps.authenticator2";
export const appleGoogleAuthenticator =
    "https://apps.apple.com/us/app/google-authenticator/id388497605";

export const androidLink = "https://images.bitnasdaq.io/bitnasdaq.apk";
export const icoEndTime = "2024-01-01";
export const facebookPageLink = "javascript:;";
export const twitterLink = "javascript:;";
export const shuftiPro = {
    url: "https://api.shuftipro.com",
    clientId:
        "d02d29d94539e536dc5e7ee7874417f6fcf6943c1ab7d07a1e89482fe2a04a65", //username
    secretKey: "hUiLtNKVnBUTxmnKoKFaGjJ69kPxQQ5v", //password
    faceJourney: "au24g8zn1693981963",
};
export const socialLinks = {
    facebook:
        "https://www.facebook.com/people/Bitnasdaq-Global/100093424770282",
    linkedin: "https://www.linkedin.com/company/bitnasdaq/",
    instagram: "https://www.instagram.com/bitnasdaq_global/",
    telegram: "https://t.me/Bitnasdaq_Global",
    discord: "https://discord.com/invite/V3AdDqwn",
    tiktok: "https://www.tiktok.com/@bitnasdaq?lang=en",
    twitter: "https://twitter.com/BitnasdaqGlobal",
    x: "https://x.com/BitnasdaqGlobal",
    youtube: "https://www.youtube.com/@Bitnasdaq",
    reddit: "https://www.reddit.com/user/Bitnasdaq",
    github: "https://github.com/Bitnasdaq",
    medium: "https://medium.com/@bitnasdaq",
};

export const workOrderUpdateTypes = {
    other: "others",
    payment: "payment",
    cryptoListing: "crypto-Listing",
    bitnasdaqVip: "bitnasdaq-Vip",
    vipProgram: "vip-Program",
    spotGame: "spot-game",
};
export const videoGuides = {
    futureTradeUrl:
        "https://www.youtube.com/embed/NE0Twepze1A?si=yZoMuP3d30FIlDUu",
    marginTradeUrl:
        "https://www.youtube.com/embed/AzL0I2qhg-g?si=hVg7ZWgS5-bs-f73",
    spotTradeUrl:
        "https://www.youtube.com/embed/kl1La0gohyM?si=cU4-Z3okUnwEKYAq",
    aboutUsGuide:
        "https://www.youtube.com/embed/6bOzEoqmLFM?si=Tt2UFGLn-t6Q7rTA",
    buyCryptoUrl:
        "https://www.youtube.com/embed/QVyaQ_HyJyE?si=QA2VkpWXkVYnZBpT",
    sellCryptoUrl:
        "https://www.youtube.com/embed/_kNP6_XKjaY?si=xD_5WGwe_2tkk9lk",
    buyBnqUrl: "https://www.youtube.com/embed/jxw6Q7rtI9Q?si=ZT9fBCHakLbVlXEU",
    bnqGuideUrl:
        "https://www.youtube.com/embed/x1hNEHfqtGA?si=IM_q7EVS8bz8nHIg",
};
export const gameRules = ["rule_1", "rule_2", "rule_3", "rule_4"];
export const channelSubtitle = {
    affiliateFaqSubtitle: "Affiliate_program_faqs",
    convertFaqSubtitle: "convert_faqs",
    strategyBotSubtitle: "strategy-bot_faqs",
    orderDetailSubtitle: "order-detail_faqs",
    identityAuthSubtitle: "identity-authentication_faqs",
    rewardhubSubtitle: "reward-hub_faqs",
    financialSubtitle: "financial_faqs",
    chatbotSubtitle: "chat-bot-questions",
    p2pHistoryFaq: "order-history_faqs",
    p2pBankTransferFaq: "p2p_banktransfer_faqs",
    p2pExpressFaq: "p2p_express_faqs",
    p2pAccountFaq: "p2p_account_faqs",
    p2pPaymentFaq: "p2p_payment_faqs",
    p2pPostingFaq: "p2p_posting_faqs",
    p2pGeneralFaq: "p2p_General_faqs",
    playcardFaqs: "bull-clash_faqs",
    playcardTerms: "bitnasdaq-bull-clash-hash-cards-terms-and-conditions",
    copyTradeTermsConditions: "bitnasdaq-copy-trading-terms-and-conditions",
    copyTradeFaqs: "copy-trade_faqs",
    invitationPoliciesSubtitle: "invitation-policies",
    calculatorFaqs: "calculator_faqs",
    investmentPlanFaqs: "investment-plan_faqs",
    whatIsBnqToken: "how-to-buy-bnq-with-bitnasdaq-convert",
    whatAreTheUsesOfBnqInEcosystem:
        "what-are-the-uses-of-bnq-in-the-bitnasdaq-ecosystem",
};

export const artileDirectLinks = {
    privactyAndSecurityTipe: `/help-dashboard/${helpCenterId}?mainChannel=${userGuide}&subChannel=${userGuide}&subItemTitle=privacy-security-tips-for-crypto`,
    cryptoFraudAndScams: `/help-dashboard/${helpCenterId}?mainChannel=${userGuide}&subChannel=${userGuide}&subItemTitle=crypto-scams-and-frauds`,
    howToAvoidPhishing: `/help-dashboard/${helpCenterId}?mainChannel=${userGuide}&subChannel=${userGuide}&subItemTitle=what-is-phishing-and-how-to-avoid`,
    bnqGuide: `/blogs/where-and-how-to-buy-bnq-step-by-step-guide`,
    paymentRateExchange: `/help-dashboard/${helpCenterId}?mainChannel=${futureChannelId}&subItemTitle=introducing-future-funding-rates-to-BitNasdaq`,
    tradeArticles: `/help-dashboard/${helpCenterId}?channelId=${futureChannelId}`,
    spotLimitMarketTriggerOrderArticle: `/help-dashboard/${helpCenterId}?mainChannel=${spotLimitMarketId}&subChannel=${spotLimitMarketId}&subItemTitle=whataremarketorhderandlimitorder`,
    marginLimitMarketTriggerOrderArticle: `/help-dashboard/${helpCenterId}?mainChannel=${marginId}&subChannel=${marginId}&subItemTitle=WhatareMarketandLimitOrdersandHowToPlaceThem`,
    copyTradeTermsConditions: `/help-dashboard/${helpCenterId}?mainChannel=${copyTradeUserGuide}&subChannel=${copyTradeUserGuide}&subItemTitle=${channelSubtitle.copyTradeTermsConditions}`,
    copyTradeFaqs: `/help-dashboard/${helpCenterId}?mainChannel=${copyTradeUserGuide}&subChannel=${copyTradeUserGuide}&subItemTitle=${channelSubtitle.copyTradeFaqs}`,
    joinMasterTrade : `/help-dashboard/${helpCenterId}?mainChannel=${copyTradeUserGuide}&subChannel=${copyTradeUserGuide}&subItemTitle=bitnasdaq-copy-trading-traders-agreement`,
    whatIsBnqToken: `/help-dashboard/${helpCenterId}?mainChannel=${bnqUserGuide}&subChannel=${bnqUserGuide}&subItemTitle=${channelSubtitle.whatIsBnqToken}`,
    whatAreTheUsesOfBnqInEcosystem: `/help-dashboard/${helpCenterId}?mainChannel=${bnqUserGuide}&subChannel=${bnqUserGuide}&subItemTitle=${channelSubtitle.whatAreTheUsesOfBnqInEcosystem}`,
};

export const chatBots = [
    {
        id: "1",
        prompt: "BNQ Token",

        answer: "For BNQ, select the option that specifies the category of your query.",
        children: [
            {
                id: "1-1",
                prompt: "About BNQ Token",
                answer: "BNQ Token, is the utility token of the BitNasdaq platform, a center of innovation in crypto. Built up on the trusted Ethereum ERC-20 chain, we here will answer any questions you have about BNQ. Please choose the question you would like to get answered.",
                children: [
                    {
                        id: "1-1-1",
                        prompt: "What is the BNQ Token?",
                        answer: "BNQ Token, is the utility token of the BitNasdaq platform, the center of innovation in the crypto realm. Unlike conventional financial instruments, BNQ is a catalyst for bringing a shift in the financial landscape, building up on the trusted Ethereum ERC-20 chain.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "1-1-1-1",
                                prompt: "How can I use the BNQ Token?",
                                answer: "Easily trade, stake, or hold your tokens, as BitNasdaq revolutionizes the trading experience for enthusiasts worldwide.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "1-1-1-2",
                                prompt: "What are the key functions of BNQ?",
                                answer: "The BNQ Token offers many key functions and features, these are: <ul><li>Utility</li><li>Trading</li><li>Staking</li><li>Governance</li><li>Rewards</li><li>Incentives</li></ul>",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "1-1-2",
                        prompt: "What are the key benefits of BNQ Token?",
                        answer: "The BNQ Token is the main utility token of the BitNasdaq exchange. Being the exchanges utility token, there are many benefits that the BNQ Token has from trading benefits, to holding benefits, to staking benefits, the BNQ Token has them all.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "1-1-2-1",
                                prompt: "List of the key benefits of the BNQ Token?",
                                answer: "Some of the key benefits of the BNQ Token are listed as below:<ul><li>High APY Rate with the BitNasdaq Financial Staking.</li><li>Spot Discounts on transaction fees.</li><li>Multiple exciting airdrop opportunities.</li><li>Access to new project tokens.</li><li>High ROI for the investments.</li><li>Profit advantages with early investment.</li></ul>",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "1-1-3",
                        prompt: "What are the benefits of ERC-20 for BNQ?",
                        answer: "BitNasdaq took a strategic step forward by focusing exclusively on the Ethereum Chain, ERC-20, for its BNQ Token. This move is designed to harness the benefits of ERC-20 and pave an easy process for developers and users alike.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "1-1-3-1",
                                prompt: "Why ERC-20 for BNQ?",
                                answer: "Ethereum's widespread adoption and infrastructure make it the optimal choice for BitNasdaq's objectives. By using Ethereum's developer community and user base, BitNasdaq aims to enhance consistency, transparency, and adoption for BNQ.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "1-1-3-2",
                                prompt: "How is ERC-20 used for BNQ Token creation?",
                                answer: "One of the primary benefits of ERC-20 tokens is the simplicity they offer to developers in creating and managing tokens. By adhering to the ERC-20 standard, developers can streamline the token creation process, eliminating the need to start from scratch.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "1-1-3-3",
                                prompt: "How secure is the ERC-20 chain for BNQ?",
                                answer: "The Ethereum blockchain's proven track record in security and reliability instils confidence in BitNasdaq's decision to migrate BNQ to ERC-20. By using Ethereum's infrastructure and consensus mechanisms, BitNasdaq aims to mitigate potential risks and guard the interests of BNQ holders.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                ],
            },
            {
                id: "1-2",
                prompt: "Get BNQ Token",
                answer: "You want to get the BNQ Token? There are few different methods of buying the BNQ Token. Each method is different and has its own step-by-step guide. Please choose the question you would like to get answered.",
                children: [
                    {
                        id: "1-2-1",
                        prompt: "Buy BNQ Tokens with BitNasdaq Spot Trading.",
                        answer: "The BNQ Token is the utility token for the BitNasdaq exchange. Owning and trading the BNQ Tokens has many benefits for its users. Users have the option to buy the BNQ Token via the Spot Trading feature available of the exchange. Follow this step-by-step guide to buy the BNQ Token with Spot Trading: <ul><li>Signup and Login to your BitNasdaq account.</li><li>Complete your Identity Verification and Account Security.</li><li>Deposit Funds into your Spot Wallet, like USDT.</li><li>Navigate to Spot Trading in Trade option available.</li><li>Select the BNQ Token and place your order.</li><li>Users can place Market, Limit, and Trigger orders.</li></ul>",
                        children: [],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "1-2-2",
                        prompt: "Buy BNQ Tokens with BitNasdaq Convert.",
                        answer: "BitNasdaq Convert makes it simple to buy BNQ tokens using USDT. Before you begin, ensure that you have USDT available in your BitNasdaq Spot Wallet. Follow this step-by-step guide to make your purchase effortlessly:<ol><li>Login to your BitNasdaq account</li><li>Navigate to the Trade button</li><li>Select the Convert option</li><li>Choose USDT and BNQ for the fields available</li><li>Click the Convert button</li><li>Review the detail receipt</li><li>Confirm the conversion</li></ol>",
                        children: [],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "1-2-3",
                        prompt: "Buy BNQ Tokens with the Instant Buy method.",
                        answer: "The Instant Buy BNQ page is a dedicated page for instantly buying the BNQ Tokens. Follow these simple steps to instantly purchase BNQ tokens on the BitNasdaq platform: <ol><li>Loing to your BitNasdaq account</li><li>Navigate to &ldquo;Buy BNQ&rdquo; option</li><li>Click the Buy BNQ button</li><li>Specify the amount of USDT</li><li>Review the final transcript</li><li>Click the Confirm button</li></ol>",
                        children: [],
                    },
                    
                ],
            },
            {
                id: "1-3",
                prompt: "BNQ Token Utility",
                answer: "The BNQ Token is the token of the BitNasdaq exchange, with its utility in many things like the trading, staking, and holding. Other than this, BNQ also many other uses. Please choose the question you would like to get answered.",
                children: [
                    {
                        id: "1-3-1",
                        prompt: "What are the uses of the BNQ Token?",
                        answer: "The BNQ Token is the main utility token on the BitNasdaq exchange. It means that the token is built and designed to run the ecosystem of the exchange. Being the utility token of the exchange, it means that the token itself has many uses on the exchange.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "1-3-1-1",
                                prompt: "What are the Staking benefits of BNQ?",
                                answer: "With the BitNasdaq Financial Staking plans, you can now stake the BNQ token for days and gain at a higher APY rate. The BitNasdaq exchange offers both Locked Savings Staking and Flexible Savings Staking plan for the BNQ token.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "1-3-1-2",
                                prompt: "What are the Trading benefits of BNQ?",
                                answer: "Trade with BNQ Token today and earn more. Be a part of the exciting world of BNQ Token trading for financial growth. The BNQ Token is available for now for Spot Trading only, where users can trade their BNQ Token by placing Market, Limit, and Trigger orders.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "1-3-1-3",
                                prompt: "What are the Hodling benefits of BNQ?",
                                answer: "Hodling BNQ is now rewarding! Win a chance to gain new project tokens, BNQ airdrop, and 20% discount on trading fee. The more BNQ Token you hodl, the more benefits there are for the user, making it the best option for long-term investors.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "1-3-2",
                        prompt: "How to Stake BNQ on BitNasdaq Financial?",
                        answer: "With the BitNasdaq Financial Staking plans, you can now stake the BNQ token for days and gain at a higher APY rate. The BitNasdaq exchange offers both Locked Savings Staking and Flexible Savings Staking plan for the BNQ token. Follow these steps to stake your BNQ Tokens: <ol><li>Login to your BitNasdaq account</li><li>Navigate to Financial staking page</li><li>Choose between Locked and Flexible Staking plans</li><li>Enter the amount of BNQ to be staked</li><li>Click the Subscribe button</li><li>Enter the 2-Factor Authentication code</li><li>Click the Subscribe button again</li></ol>",
                        children: [],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "1-3-3",
                        prompt: "What are the uses of BNQ in the BitNasdaq Ecosystem?",
                        answer: "The BNQ Token is the utility token of the BitNasdaq exchange, and not only this, it is the versatile token of the exchange, building the ecosystem of the exchange.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "1-3-3-1",
                                prompt: "What are some of BNQ ecosystem utility?",
                                answer: "The versatility of BNQ extends far beyond its initial benefits, offering users a diverse range of practical applications. From investment opportunities to enhanced financial security and reduced exchange fees, BNQ empowers users to explore financial growth and stability.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "1-3-3-2",
                                prompt: "What is the BNQ Staking plan?",
                                answer: "One of the prominent uses of BNQ within the BitNasdaq ecosystem is staking. Through BitNasdaq's Financial Staking plans, users can stake their BNQ tokens for a specified duration and earn attractive rewards at a higher APY rate.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "1-3-3-3",
                                prompt: "How important is BNQ for BitNasdaq ecosystem?",
                                answer: "With BNQ, BitNasdaq is revolutionizing the trading experience for cryptocurrency enthusiasts worldwide, offering easy integration of innovative features and unparalleled opportunities for financial empowerment.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "1-3-4",
                        prompt: "Is there an Investment Plan for the BNQ Token?",
                        answer: "The BitNasdaq Investment Plan, for the investor by the investor, focusing on innovation, and your one-way ticket to sky-high ROI and a chance to be a part of BitNasdaq's explosive growth. Invest with the BitNasdaq Investment Plan and watch your investments grow alongside us.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "1-3-4-1",
                                prompt: "How to buy the BNQ Investment Plan?",
                                answer: "Follow these steps carefully, and buy your chosen plan with the BitNasdaq Investment Plan: <ul><li>Signup and login to your BitNasdaq account</li><li>Complete your Identity Verification</li><li>Complete your Account Security</li><li>Deposit USDT in your BitNasdaq account</li><li>Navigate to the Investment plan in header</li><li>Select from 3 different Investment Plans available</li><li>Purchase the plan that best suits you</li></ul>",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "1-3-4-2",
                                prompt: "What is the mission of the Investment Plan?",
                                answer: "The mission of the BitNasdaq Investment Plan is to empower investors by providing structured, secure, and high-ROI investment opportunities within the cryptocurrency market.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "1-3-4-3",
                                prompt: "What is the vision of the Investment Plan?",
                                answer: "Our vision is to transform BitNasdaq into the Nasdaq of the Blockchain Industry, where innovation, growth, and investor prosperity are at the forefront.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "1-3-4-4",
                                prompt: "What is the Future of the Investment Plan?",
                                answer: "The future of the BitNasdaq Investment Plan is rooted in our commitment to continuous innovation and growth. As we expand our user base and community, we see the BNQ Token becoming a major part of the blockchain industry, offering new financial opportunities and features that drive investment success.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                ],
            },
            {
                id: "1-4",
                prompt: "BNQ Trading",
                answer: "The BNQ Token is the utility token of the BitNasdaq exchange, and one of the biggest advantages of BNQ is that users can trade BNQ and earn high profits. Please choose the question you would like to get answered.",
                children: [
                    {
                        id: "1-4-1",
                        prompt: "How to trade BNQ Tokens?",
                        answer: "The BNQ Token is the utility token for the BitNasdaq exchange. Users have the option to Spot Trade the BNQ Token via the Spot Trading feature available of the exchange for now. Here is a simple step-by-step guide on completing Spot Trading of BNQ on the BitNasdaq exchange. <ol><li>Log on or sign up on BitNasdaq.</li><li>Click on Trade and then Spot.</li><li>The are Limit Orders, where you can trade your BNQ for a specific price.</li><li>Market Orders, where you can trade BNQ for the real-time market price value.</li><li>Trigger Orders, enables you the advanced option of trading between two price points.</li></ol>",
                        children: [],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "1-4-2",
                        prompt: "What are the benefits of trading BNQs?",
                        answer: "The BNQ Token is the utility token for the BitNasdaq exchange. Owning and trading the BNQ Tokens has many benefits for its users. These benefits make the BNQ Token a must have for all its users. Users have the option to Spot Trade the BNQ Token via the Spot Trading feature available of the exchange for now.",
                        children: [],
                    },
                ],
            },
        ],
    },
    {
        id: "2",
        prompt: "P2P Trading",
        answer: "For P2P, select the option that specifies the category of your query.",
        children: [
            {
                id: "2-1",
                prompt: "P2P Trading",
                answer: "",
                children: [
                    {
                        id: "2-1-1",
                        prompt: "What is P2P Trading?",
                        answer: "P2P trading, or peer-to-peer trading in cryptocurrency, involves the direct exchange of digital assets between individuals on a cryptocurrency exchanges. Operating on decentralized platforms or centralized platforms, P2P trading utilizes blockchain technology and smart contracts to facilitate direct transactions.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-1-1-1",
                                prompt: "What happens during P2P Trade?",
                                answer: "Users create ads, specifying the cryptocurrency, desired price, and preferred payment method. An escrow service is employed to secure transactions, holding funds until both parties have fulfilled their obligations.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-1-1-2",
                                prompt: "How are P2P Trade marked as complete?",
                                answer: "Upon confirmation, the cryptocurrency is released to the buyer's wallet, marking the completion of the trade. P2P trading offers privacy, direct ownership, flexibility, and global accessibility.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-1-1-3",
                                prompt: "What basic security should be used by P2P Traders?",
                                answer: "To mitigate risks, users are advised to enable two-factor authentication, set up a funds password, and conduct thorough research on how to complete a P2P Transaction.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-1-2",
                        prompt: "How to Buy Crypto in P2P?",
                        answer: "Begin by logging into your BitNasdaq account and navigating to the dedicated P2P trading section for peer-to-peer cryptocurrency transactions. In the Buy section, choose your desired cryptocurrency from the available options and select a buying option that aligns with your preferences.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-1-2-1",
                                prompt: "What trading parameters needs to be set?",
                                answer: "Set parameters for the purchase, such as the quantity, price, and any additional requirements. Before proceeding, carefully review all trade details, ensuring accuracy in price, quantity, payment method, and terms. Click the 'Buy' button when ready to initiate the purchase and notify potential sellers.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-1-2-2",
                                prompt: "When will the seller release the amount from escrow?",
                                answer: "Follow the seller's payment instructions, make the payment using the agreed-upon method, and double-check all details before sending funds. Once payment is made, notify the seller and provide the necessary proof. The seller verifies the payment and releases the cryptocurrency from the escrow account.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-1-2-3",
                                prompt: "Where can I check order history?",
                                answer: "Upon receiving the cryptocurrency in your BitNasdaq wallet, the trade is complete and can be checked in your Order History.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-1-3",
                        prompt: "How to Sell Crypto in P2P?",
                        answer: "Begin by logging into your BitNasdaq account and navigating to the dedicated P2P trading section. Within the P2P trading Sell section, select the desired sell option from the available ads, considering rates that align with your preferences.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-1-3-1",
                                prompt: "What trading parameters needs to be set?",
                                answer: "Specify your parameters, including cryptocurrency amount, desired payment, and any additional requirements. Prior to proceeding, review trade details such as price, quantity, and payment method. Once satisfied, click 'Sell' to initiate the order and alert potential merchants.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-1-3-2",
                                prompt: "When should I release the amount from escrow?",
                                answer: "After the merchant sends your due diligence amount, confirm receipt, triggering the option to finalize the payment transfer. Completing verification concludes the process and your P2P selling is complete.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-1-4",
                        prompt: "How does P2P Trading work?",
                        answer: "Users on BitNasdaq can create ads expressing their intent to buy or sell specific cryptocurrencies, detailing quantity and preferred prices. The platform's interface allows buyers to browse ads, evaluating options based on various factors.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-1-4-1",
                                prompt: "Is there a messaging facility on BitNasdaq P2P?",
                                answer: "Secure messaging ensures efficient communication between buyers and sellers. P2P trading on BitNasdaq enables setting trade terms, including price and payment methods, leading to a customized and fair exchange.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-1-4-2",
                                prompt: "Does BitNasdaq have an escrow service?",
                                answer: "Once terms are settled, the platform acts as a secure escrow service, facilitating trade execution. After completion, BitNasdaq ensures a swift settlement process, releasing funds to the seller and providing buyers instant access to their acquired assets.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-1-5",
                        prompt: "Are the offers on P2P market provided by BitNasdaq?",
                        answer: "No, the offers you see on the P2P market are not offered by BitNasdaq. BitNasdaq serves as a platform to facilitate P2P trading, but the offers are provided by users and merchants on an individual basis.",
                        children: [],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-1-6",
                        prompt: "How secure is P2P trading?",
                        answer: "The security of P2P trading is a significant concern. BitNasdaq employs secure escrow services, two-factor authentication, encryption, and funds password. Verification processes, serve as a crucial layer of security by ensuring the legitimacy of participants.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-1-6-1",
                                prompt: "Does BitNasdaq have educational content for security?",
                                answer: "Education about common scams and cautious dealings is advised, along with public trades and secure messaging to mitigate risks in P2P transactions. While P2P cryptocurrency trading has its unique challenges, BitNasdaq serves as a means of secure P2P Trading.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                ],
            },
            {
                id: "2-2",
                prompt: "P2P Merchant",
                answer: "A P2P Merchant is an advertiser on the P2P market. The merchant can post buy ads and sell ads on the exchange, gaining other exclusive benefits and tools as well. Please choose the question you would like to get answered.",
                children: [
                    {
                        id: "2-2-1",
                        prompt: "Who are P2P Merchants?",
                        answer: "A P2P Merchant is an advertiser on the P2P market. The merchant can post buy ads and sell ads on the exchange. Becoming a P2P merchant on BitNasdaq is a straightforward process, offering an expanded audience and contributing to the growth of the cryptocurrency community.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-2-1-1",
                                prompt: "Does BitNasdaq support P2P Merchants?",
                                answer: "As cryptocurrencies gain mainstream acceptance, the role of P2P merchants becomes increasingly vital, and BitNasdaq's commitment to innovation positions it as a driving force in shaping the future of P2P transactions in the cryptocurrency landscape.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-2-2",
                        prompt: "What are the benefits for BitNasdaq P2P Merchants?",
                        answer: "BitNasdaq aims to establish a user-friendly trading platform, emphasizing easy P2P Trading interface with hassle-free ad posting. Becoming P2P Merchants, users can post buy and sell ads on BitNasdaq, unlocking numerous benefits.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-2-2-1",
                                prompt: "What more benefits do Merchants have?",
                                answer: "BitNasdaq's commitment is further demonstrated through exclusive customer support, ensuring P2P Merchants receive prompt assistance, creating an ecosystem where they can grow in the cryptocurrency landscape.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-2-3",
                        prompt: "How to become a P2P Merchant?",
                        answer: "Becoming a P2P Merchant on the BitNasdaq platform is easy that involves a few simple steps. After logging into your BitNasdaq account, navigate to the P2P dashboard and select the Post New Ad section. Locate the 'Become Merchant' button, click it, and you'll be directed to the P2P Merchant Application page.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-2-3-1",
                                prompt: "What are the prerequisites for becoming a Merchant?",
                                answer: "Before achieving P2P Merchant status, ensure you deposit a minimum of 1500 USDT in your P2P Wallet and complete the necessary KYC requirements. Once these steps are completed, you can confirm the application terms and officially become a P2P Merchant on BitNasdaq.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-2-4",
                        prompt: "How to get a Verified Merchant Certificate?",
                        answer: "To achieve this status, users must deposit 1500 USDT, engage in a specified number of trades, maintain a high trade completion rate, and accumulate a substantial number of completed orders. The platform's commitment to trustworthiness is evident with setting these criteria, ensuring financial stability and active contribution to liquidity.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-2-4-1",
                                prompt: "What are the benefits of being a Verified Merchant?",
                                answer: "Verified merchants enjoy increased trust and order placements, as well as a visual representation of credibility through BitNasdaq, creating a secure and transparent trading environment.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-2-4-2",
                                prompt: "What will the Verified badge do for me?",
                                answer: "Obtaining a Verified Merchant Certificate is seen as a strategic move for serious cryptocurrency traders, contributing to the growth and stability of BitNasdaq's community.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-2-5",
                        prompt: "How do Merchants post ads?",
                        answer: "BitNasdaq offers a user-friendly platform for buying and selling digital assets, with a focus on empowering merchants to post new ads easily. Before getting started, merchants undergo a crucial verification process to ensure the security and legitimacy of transactions.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-2-5-1",
                                prompt: "Do Merchants have to add a payment method?",
                                answer: "Once verified, they can add a payment method through the P2P dashboard, which serves as the central hub for managing various aspects of the trading experience.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-2-5-2",
                                prompt: "Can Merchants post both buy and sell ads?",
                                answer: "The dashboard allows merchants to choose between posting buy or sell ads, catering to their specific trading objectives.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-2-5-3",
                                prompt: "How can the ad be posted?",
                                answer: "After inputting the necessary information, a simple click on the 'Post Ad' button finalizes the process, enabling merchants to engage swiftly with BitNasdaq's cryptocurrency traders community.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-2-6",
                        prompt: "What are the verification requirements for a P2P Merchant?",
                        answer: "BitNasdaq has established stringent verification requirements for individuals aspiring to become P2P Merchants on the platform.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-2-6-1",
                                prompt: "What basic verifications are required?",
                                answer: "The process begins with email verification, establishing a secure communication channel. Phone number verification adds an extra layer of security against unauthorized access.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-2-6-2",
                                prompt: "Is KYC important for Merchants?",
                                answer: "P2P Merchants must then complete Know Your Customer (KYC) processes, emphasizing accurate and up-to-date information to comply with regulatory standards.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-2-6-3",
                                prompt: "What additional security requirements are needed for Merchants?",
                                answer: "Two-Factor Authentication (2FA) further fortifies account security, and a Funds Password is required to secure financial transactions.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-2-6-4",
                                prompt: "Do Merchants have to deposit funds in P2P wallet?",
                                answer: "Additionally, a 1500 USDT deposit to the P2P wallet demonstrates commitment and guards against fraudulent activities.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-2-6-5",
                                prompt: "Is there a Merchant Agreement in BitNasdaq?",
                                answer: "P2P Merchants must adhere to BitNasdaq's P2P Advertiser Agreement, outlining terms and conditions, before submitting their application, a final step signifying readiness for a secure and transparent trading experience in the cryptocurrency world.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                ],
            },
            {
                id: "2-3",
                prompt: "Crypto Withdrawals",
                answer: "Crypto withdrawals are the movement of crypto from one wallet to another. In withdrawals, the crypto is transferred to an external wallet address off of the current exchange or digital wallet. Please choose the question you would like to get answered.",
                children: [
                    {
                        id: "2-3-1",
                        prompt: "Can I withdraw crypto from my P2P wallet?",
                        answer: "BitNasdaq's P2P Wallet is a crucial tool for cryptocurrency traders that are looking for P2P Trades. The platform's P2P Wallet facilitates trading between users, but a common question arises, can one withdraw crypto directly from this wallet? The answer is NO.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-3-1-1",
                                prompt: "How can I then convert my crypto to fiat currency?",
                                answer: "BitNasdaq has a structured process that involves converting crypto holdings into fiat currency through P2P selling within the trading dashboard. To initiate withdrawal, users navigate to the 'Sell' section, filter through sell ads based on criteria, and place a sell order.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-3-1-2",
                                prompt: "What does the sell process entail?",
                                answer: "This process converts digital assets into fiat currency, which can then be withdrawn from the BitNasdaq platform. Essentially, P2P trading is the key mechanism for users to effectively manage and withdraw their crypto holdings on BitNasdaq.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-3-2",
                        prompt: "How to withdraw crypto from my P2P wallet?",
                        answer: "BitNasdaq's P2P Wallet provides cryptocurrency traders with a solution to easily convert their digital assets into fiat currency. Before withdrawing funds, users must understand that direct withdrawal from the P2P Wallet is NOT possible.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-3-2-1",
                                prompt: "Where can I convert my currency to fiat currency?",
                                answer: "The process begins by logging into the BitNasdaq account and navigating to the P2P dashboard, the central hub for all P2P transactions. Within the dashboard, users explore the 'Sell' section, where different sell ads to preferences and requirements are available. Finding the perfect match involves considering factors such as price, payment methods, crypto amount for sale, and additional seller requirements.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-3-2-2",
                                prompt: "What does the sell option entail for P2P users?",
                                answer: "Once a suitable sell ad is identified, users place a sell order through the user-friendly interface, specifying details like the quantity of crypto to sell, agreed-upon price, and any additional requirements. The sale is executed through BitNasdaq's secure P2P trading platform, and upon successful completion, users can withdraw the converted fiat currency from the platform.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-3-2-3",
                                prompt: "Is converting my crypto to fiat done via BitNasdaq P2P Trade?",
                                answer: "In essence, BitNasdaq's P2P trade mechanism serves as the key to withdrawing fiat currency from the platform in exchange for cryptocurrencies. This offers a secure and verified transaction environment.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                ],
            },
            {
                id: "2-4",
                prompt: "Order Dispute",
                answer: "For traders encountering disputes can be a hassle, but it is something that happens. But don’t worry, BitNasdaq is here to help you overcome these order disputes. Please choose the question you would like to get answered.",
                children: [
                    {
                        id: "2-4-1",
                        prompt: "What to do if there is a P2P dispute?",
                        answer: "Occasional disputes can challenge the security and fairness of P2P transactions. BitNasdaq recognizes the need for a smooth trading experience and offers help for handling P2P disputes.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-4-1-1",
                                prompt: "What is the first step in resolving P2P disputes?",
                                answer: "Effective communication is the initial step, encouraging open dialogue between trading partners to resolve issues amicably. Thoroughly reviewing transaction details, such as payment and ID information, is crucial before escalating the matter.",
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-4-1-2",
                                prompt: "Does BitNasdaq offer an Appeal option?",
                                answer: "BitNasdaq provides an Appeal as a next step, where users can present evidence for mediation by the support team. Transparency is key when presenting evidence, including screenshots and communication logs, to aid in a fair decision.",
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-4-1-3",
                                prompt: "How much time can dispute resolution take?",
                                answer: "Adhering to platform guidelines for P2P trading and exercising patience throughout the resolution process is emphasized, ensuring a positive trading experience on BitNasdaq's secure and reliable platform.",
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-4-2",
                        prompt: "How to submit a P2P appeal?",
                        answer: "The BitNasdaq P2P trading interface has an easy system for submitting appeals and resolving any dispute that may appear. Whenever a user has any dispute, they can use the Appeal button to get a resolution. If the buyer causes an issue, or the seller, either way, users have the option to open an appeal.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-4-2-1",
                                prompt: "What details should be submitted for an Appeal?",
                                answer: "Users have to click on the Appeal Button, where they must submit screenshots of the trade history, any conversation made for the deal, and any other information.",
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-4-2-2",
                                prompt: "Does BitNasdaq act as an intermediary?",
                                answer: "Once the user submits the appeal, BitNasdaq will become an intermediary and resolve the issue for the users as quickly as possible.",
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-4-3",
                        prompt: "Coin has not been released by the seller.",
                        answer: "The BitNasdaq trading platform has a feature set in place specifically for issues like these. The BitNasdaq platform has an escrow service, where the coins are stored. In case a seller does not fulfill the requirement of the trade, the BitNasdaq platform will freeze the coins in escrow to prevent any fraud.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-4-3-1",
                                prompt: "What are the benefits of an escrow?",
                                answer: "The escrow service ensures that the terms of the trade are met from the buyers' and sellers’ end. Only once the requirements are met and fulfilled, the coins are released from escrow.",
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-4-3-2",
                                prompt: "What are the benefits of an appeal?",
                                answer: "The second case is the appeal option available to all P2P traders on BitNasdaq. With this option, traders just need to submit all the necessary screenshots and requirements of the trade and let BitNasdaq act as an intermediary to resolve the matter.",
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-4-3-3",
                                prompt: "What are the benefits of opening a ticket?",
                                answer: "If this still does not work out for the users, they can open a formal ticket on the BitNasdaq platform, over at the Contact Us page. On this page, the users can submit their queries, and the BitNasdaq team will get in touch with them.",
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-4-4",
                        prompt: "I have overpaid the seller.",
                        answer: "If you've overpaid the seller, your first course of action should be to utilize the BitNasdaq communication interface available in the P2P section. This interface provides users with a means to communicate freely to resolve any issues that may arise during the transaction process.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-4-4-1",
                                prompt: "What are the benefits of Appeal in this situation?",
                                answer: "Should your attempts to communicate with the seller prove unsuccessful, or if the seller is unresponsive, you can escalate the matter by opening an appeal for the trade. BitNasdaq's platform offers an appeal option specifically tailored for P2P trading scenarios. Our experienced support team works diligently to address appeals promptly and impartially, striving to reach a resolution that is equitable for all parties involved.",
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-4-5",
                        prompt: "The seller is charging extra now.",
                        answer: "The first rule of engaging in cryptocurrency trades on BitNasdaq is to adhere strictly to the agreed-upon terms. When you initiate a trade, the price at which the trade is opened serves as the mutual agreement between the buyer and the seller. Under no circumstances should you agree to pay extra beyond this agreed-upon price.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-4-5-1",
                                prompt: "What should I do if seller insists on extra money?",
                                answer: "The moment you notice any deviation from the agreed-upon terms, cancel the order immediately. Additionally, make sure to report the seller or merchant to BitNasdaq. Charging extra could be a red flag indicating a potential scam or fraudulent behavior on the seller's part.",
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-4-5-2",
                                prompt: "Can the Appeal help in this situation?",
                                answer: "In unfortunate cases where you've already made payment, but the seller refuses to release the cryptocurrency without demanding additional funds, it's time to escalate the matter. BitNasdaq offers a recourse mechanism for such P2P disputes through its appeal process.",
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-4-5-3",
                                prompt: "How does BitNasdaq resolve such matters?",
                                answer: "BitNasdaq's primary objective during the dispute resolution process is to ensure fairness and protect the interests of its users. Upon reviewing the evidence presented, BitNasdaq will make a decision aimed at resolving the dispute promptly and equitably.",
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-4-6",
                        prompt: "Payment not received from the buyer.",
                        answer: "For every P2P trade facilitated on BitNasdaq, a time limit is set, typically ranging from 15 minutes to 1 hour. If the buyer fails to send the payment within this stipulated time, rest assured that our system automatically cancels the order.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-4-6-1",
                                prompt: "Can I chat with the buyer on BitNasdaq P2P?",
                                answer: "If the buyer is online but hasn't initiated the payment process, users can leverage the BitNasdaq communication interface available within the P2P trade platform. This interface serves as a direct channel for communication between parties involved in the transaction.",
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-4-6-2",
                                prompt: "Can the Appeal option help me in this situation?",
                                answer: "At BitNasdaq, we understand the importance of trust and confidence within our trading community. As such, we take on the role of an intermediary to facilitate smooth transactions and address any issues that may arise along the way with the Appeal option.",
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-4-7",
                        prompt: "The buyer has underpaid.",
                        answer: "When facing an underpayment issue, the first course of action is to leverage the communication features available within BitNasdaq's P2P Trade interface. This interface provides users with a direct channel to communicate openly with the buyer or merchant involved in the transaction.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-4-7-1",
                                prompt: "Can I use the appeal option in this case?",
                                answer: "If communication fails for a resolution, BitNasdaq offers an Appeal option to all its users. This appeal process serves as a formal mechanism for addressing disputes and discrepancies in P2P trades. To initiate an Appeal, users must provide relevant evidence to support their claim.",
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-4-7-2",
                                prompt: "What steps should I take if the buyer has underpaid?",
                                answer: "If you find yourself in a situation where the buyer has underpaid, remember to communicate openly and utilize BitNasdaq's appeal process for a fair resolution.",
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-4-8",
                        prompt: "I have encountered a scammer, how to avoid them?",
                        answer: "Encountering scammers, frauds, phishing schemes, and Ponzi schemes in the world of crypto is unfortunately not uncommon. BitNasdaq understands the importance of keeping our users safe from such malicious actors. If you ever find yourself in a situation where you've encountered a scammer while engaging in P2P Trading on BitNasdaq, here's what you should do:<ul><li>Double-Check Your Wallet/Bank Account</li><li>Avoid Third-Party Payments</li><li>Release Funds After Receiving Payment</li><li>Don't Trust External Offers or Information</li><li>Don't Rush Transactions</li><li>Avoid Cancelling Orders After Payment</li><li>Staying Vigilant</li><li>Reporting Suspected Scams</li></ul>",
                        children: [],
                    },
                ],
            },
            {
                id: "2-5",
                prompt: "Order Cancellation",
                answer: "For traders engaging in P2P Trading, canceling orders is a common matter that can occur. Users may need to cancel their orders based on the situation. BitNasdaq is here to resolve any query you have regarding order cancellations. Please choose the question you would like to get answered.",
                children: [
                    {
                        id: "2-5-1",
                        prompt: "How to cancel an open order?",
                        answer: "If you've placed an order on BitNasdaq's P2P Trading and wish to cancel it, the process is simple. Find the open trade you want to cancel. Open the trade, and on the trade interface, click on the cancel button associated with it. This action initiates the cancellation process.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-5-1-1",
                                prompt: "Do I need to give reasons for cancellation?",
                                answer: "After clicking the cancel button, BitNasdaq will prompt you to select a reason for canceling the order. This step helps BitNasdaq understand users' needs better and improve its services. Choose the reason that best describes why you're canceling the order.",
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-5-2",
                        prompt: "What is the time frame for order cancellation?",
                        answer: "When placing a buy order on BitNasdaq, users are granted a 30-minute window for order cancellation. Within this timeframe, traders have the autonomy to cancel their buy orders at their discretion. It's important to note that this window begins as soon as the buy order is placed. Upon placing a sell order, users are required to wait for a duration of 30 minutes. If, after this time, the trade remains unconcluded, BitNasdaq automatically cancels the sell order.",
                        children: [],
                    },
                ],
            },
            {
                id: "2-6",
                prompt: "Express Trade",
                answer: "Express Trade is a feature that allows users to quickly and easily buy or sell cryptocurrencies using a simplified interface of P2P Trade. Please choose the question you would like to get answered.",
                children: [
                    {
                        id: "2-6-1",
                        prompt: "What is Express Trade?",
                        answer: "Express Trade is a feature that allows users to quickly and easily buy or sell cryptocurrencies using a simplified interface of P2P Trading. It offers a simple process for executing trades at the current market price, based on the live orders available on the P2P interface by various merchants.",
                        children: [],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-6-2",
                        prompt: "How does Express Trade work?",
                        answer: "Express Trade is a feature that allows users to quickly and easily buy or sell cryptocurrencies in P2P Trading.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-6-2-1",
                                prompt: "How does Express Trade work for buying cryptocurrencies?",
                                answer: "For users looking to purchase cryptocurrencies, the process is simple. They specify the amount of money in fiat currency they wish to spend and the amount of the desired cryptocurrency they want to acquire.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-6-2-2",
                                prompt: "How does Express Trade work for selling cryptocurrencies?",
                                answer: "For those looking to sell their cryptocurrencies, Express Trade offers a hassle-free solution. Users specify the amount of cryptocurrency they want to sell and the desired amount of money they wish to receive in fiat currency.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-6-3",
                        prompt: "How are the merchants matched in Express Trade?",
                        answer: "In Express Trade, whenever a user initiates a buy order or a sell order, they are automatically matched to the merchants ads that are available on the exchange.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-6-3-1",
                                prompt: "How will I be matched if I place a buy order?",
                                answer: "When users intend to buy cryptocurrencies through Express Trade, they specify the amount of money in fiat currency they wish to invest, along with the quantity of coins they desire to purchase. The express interface then automatically matches the user with a suitable merchant from the P2P trading ads.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-6-3-2",
                                prompt: "How will I be matched if I place a sell order?",
                                answer: "For those looking to sell their cryptocurrencies, users input the quantity of crypto they aim to sell, along with the desired amount of fiat currency they wish to receive. Similar to the buying process, the express interface promptly identifies and matches the user with an appropriate merchant from the P2P trading ads.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-6-4",
                        prompt: "Is Express Trade Safe?",
                        answer: "Express Trade is absolutely safe on the BitNasdaq cryptocurrency exchange. BitNasdaq understands the paramount importance of security in the trade of digital assets.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-6-4-1",
                                prompt: "What measures is BitNasdaq taking to keep my assets safe?",
                                answer: "BitNasdaq employs state-of-the-art encryption protocols to ensure that user's personal data and transaction details remain confidential. Additionally, the exchange utilizes industry-standard security practices to protect against unauthorized access and fraudulent activities.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-6-4-2",
                                prompt: "Can there still be some risks involved in Express Trade?",
                                answer: "While BitNasdaq provides a secure environment for Express Trade, users must exercise caution when trading cryptocurrencies. Despite stringent security measures, the cryptocurrency market can be volatile, and risks abound.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-6-4-3",
                                prompt: "What can I do to stay safe when trading?",
                                answer: "One crucial aspect of ensuring the safety of Express Trade on BitNasdaq is verifying the merchants involved in the transactions. While BitNasdaq diligently vets merchants on its platform, users should also take proactive steps to verify the legitimacy of their trading partners.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                ],
            },
            {
                id: "2-7",
                prompt: "Bank Transfer & Payment",
                answer: "A bank transfer is needed for P2P Trading, BitNasdaq here will resolve your queries about bank transfer and payment issues. Please choose the question you would like to get answered.",
                children: [
                    {
                        id: "2-7-1",
                        prompt: "How do you add a payment method to P2P Trading?",
                        answer: "For completing P2P trades and transactions on BitNasdaq, you need to add a fiat currency payment method. <ul><li>Access the P2P dashboard</li><li>go to the P2P Payment Methods</li><li>choose Add Payment Method</li><li>select the payment method</li><li>fill in the payment details</li><li>confirm the payment method</li></ul>",
                        children: [],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-7-2",
                        prompt: "How are payments handled in P2P trading?",
                        answer: "On BitNasdaq, this process is simple to offer convenience and security for users. Payments in P2P trading are typically made directly between the buyer and the seller. This direct interaction eliminates the need for intermediaries, resulting in faster transactions and reduced fees. A variety of payment methods are available to users on BitNasdaq, from traditional bank transfers to digital payment platforms.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-7-2-1",
                                prompt: "What payment methods are available for P2P Trading?",
                                answer: "One of the key elements that make P2P trading efficient and accessible is the variety of payment methods available to users on BitNasdaq. From traditional bank transfers to digital payment platforms, BitNasdaq offers a range of options to cater to diverse preferences.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-7-3",
                        prompt: "What is an escrow service in P2P trading?",
                        answer: "An escrow service acts as a trusted intermediary that safeguards the funds or cryptocurrency involved in a P2P trade.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-7-3-1",
                                prompt: "Does BitNasdaq have an escrow service?",
                                answer: "During a P2P trade on BitNasdaq, the escrow service securely holds the funds until both parties have fulfilled their obligations in the transaction.",
                                children: []
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-7-3-2",
                                prompt: "How does BitNasdaq enable secure payment?",
                                answer: "BitNasdaq takes numerous measures to secure P2P trades on its platform. By providing an escrow service, funds password, and 2-FA, they add an extra layer of security for users.",
                                children: []
                            }
                        ]
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-7-4",
                        prompt: "Can I use fiat currency for payments in P2P trading?",
                        answer: "Yes, BitNasdaq's P2P trade facilitates the exchange of cryptocurrencies for fiat currency. This means users can transact using traditional currencies such as the US Dollar, Euro, or any other fiat currency supported by the platform. The platform's support for fiat transactions, coupled with a variety of payment methods, empowers users to engage in cryptocurrency trading with ease and confidence.",
                        children: []
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-7-5",
                        prompt: "Are there any transaction fees associated with P2P trading payments?",
                        answer: "One of the common concerns among traders is the transaction fees that may eat into their profits. However, at BitNasdaq, users can engage in P2P trading without worrying about any trading fees.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-7-5-1",
                                prompt: "What are the benefits of no fee in P2P?",
                                answer: "The absence of trading fees associated with P2P trading on BitNasdaq offers several advantages to users. Firstly, it ensures transparency and fairness in transactions, as there are no hidden costs or surprises for traders. Additionally, fee-free trading encourages greater participation in the P2P marketplace, attracting both seasoned traders and newcomers alike.",
                                children: []
                            }
                        ]
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-7-6",
                        prompt: "What Are The Common Payment Methods Used For P2P?",
                        answer: "One of the key elements that make P2P trading efficient and accessible is the variety of payment methods available to users. Bank transfers are common payment method in P2P trading on BitNasdaq. The advantage of bank transfers lies in their global accessibility and reliability.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-7-6-1",
                                prompt: "Can I make payments via Digital Wallets and Digital platforms?",
                                answer: "Digital payment platforms have gained significant traction in recent years, making them a widely accepted method in P2P trading on BitNasdaq. Platforms like PayPal, Venmo, and Skrill offer convenient and fast payment options for traders.",
                                children: []
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                ],
            },
            {
                id: "2-8",
                prompt: "Ads Posting",
                answer: "Posting P2P ads on BitNasdaq is very simple, and you can post your ads in the P2P dashboard on BitNasdaq. Merchants can post ads for both buying and selling their assets. Please choose the question you would like to get answered.",
                children: [
                    {
                        id: "2-8-1",
                        prompt: "How can I post ads on BitNasdaq?",
                        answer: "To post a P2P Ad on the BitNasdaq platform, users need to apply to become a merchant. Once a merchant, users can easily post Buy and Sell Ads on the exchange. Follow these steps to post an ad after you have become a merchant:<ul><li>Log in to your BitNasdaq Account</li><li>Navigate to the P2P Trading Section</li><li>Choose the 'Post New Ad' Option</li><li>Select 'I Want To Sell' or 'I Want To Buy'</li><li>Fill in the Required Information</li></ul>",
                        children: []
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-8-2",
                        prompt: "Can I post ads without becoming a merchant?",
                        answer: "The simple answer is that users CANNOT post ads on the BitNasdaq exchange unless they become merchants. Becoming a merchant is the first initial step in posting ads on the BitNasdaq exchange.",
                        children: []
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-8-3",
                        prompt: "How do you post a sell ad?",
                        answer: "Posting a Sell Ad on the BitNasdaq P2P Trading interface is very simple. All you need to do is follow this simple step-by-step guide:<ul><li>Click on the Buy Crypto on your screen.</li><li>In the P2P dashboard, you will find the Post New Ad section.</li><li>Click on that section.</li><li>On this page, select the 'I Want To Sell' section.</li><li>Select the asset you want to sell.</li><li>Select the fiat currency you want to sell it for.</li><li>Add all the requirements asked for.Agree to the terms, and post your ad.</li><li>Agree to the terms, and post your ad.</li></ul>",
                        children: []
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-8-4",
                        prompt: "How do you post a buy ad?",
                        answer: "Posting a Buy Ad on the BitNasdaq P2P Trading is easy and simple. All you need to do is follow this simple step-by-step guide:<ul><li>Click on the Buy Crypto on your screen.</li><li>In the P2P dashboard, you will find the Post New Ad section.</li><li>Click on that section.</li><li>On this page select the I Want To Buy section.</li><li>Select the asset you want to buy.</li><li>Select the fiat currency you want to buy it with.</li><li>Add all the requirements asked for.</li><li>Agree to the terms, and post your ad.</li></ul>",
                        children: []
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-8-5",
                        prompt: "What are the requirements for ad posting?",
                        answer: "Posting an ad on the BitNasdaq exchange’s P2P Trading is very simple. The first requirement for posting an ad on BitNasdaq P2P Trading is for the user to become a Merchant. You can apply to become a merchant via the merchant form in the P2P dashboard. Once the user becomes a merchant, they can then post both buy ads and sell ads on the exchange.",
                        children: []
                    }
                ]
            },            
            {
                id: "2-9",
                prompt: "Account Setup",
                answer: "To start P2P Trading on the BitNasdaq platform, users must setup their account. Setting up your account on BitNasdaq is very simple. Please choose the question you would like to get answered.",
                children: [
                    {
                        id: "2-9-1",
                        prompt: "P2P Trading is an exciting avenue for traders that are looking to buy and sell cryptocurrencies against fiat currencies. P2P enables users to buy and sell their cryptocurrencies on the ads that are posted by merchant, and users can become a merchant and place their own buy and sell ads. To setup your P2P Account, all users have to do is setup their BitNasdaq account.",
                        answer: "",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-9-1-1",
                                prompt: "How can I setup my account on BitNasdaq?",
                                answer: "Follow this step-by-step guide and set your account and ready for BitNasdaq and P2P Trading:<ul><li>Signup on BitNasdaq with email and password</li><li>Complete your primary verification and KYC</li><li>Comple your 2-Factor authentication</li><li>Setup a strong Funds Password.</li></ul>",
                                children: []
                            },
                        ]
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-9-2",
                        prompt: "What are the requirements for P2P Account Setup?",
                        answer: "To set up your account for P2P Trading users first have to sign up on BitNasdaq. When a user signs up on BitNasdaq and completes its requirements, their P2P Trading account is set up automatically. These requirements are: <ul><li>Valid email address</li><li>Strong account password</li><li>Nickname of choice</li><li>Valid phone number</li><li>Personal information like DOB</li><li>Valid government issued ID</li><li>Clear pictures for facial recognition</li><li>Google Authenticator for 2-FA</li><li>Strong Funds Password</li></ul>",
                        children: []
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-9-3",
                        prompt: "Is KYC important for P2P Account Setup?",
                        answer: "KYC is necessary for using the full features of the BitNasdaq exchange. This includes higher limits for trading, the P2P features, higher limits for P2P trading, higher limits for internal transfer of funds, higher limits for coin withdrawals, and more. These features become available just as the KYC is approved by the exchange, thus making the KYC process important for P2P Account Setup.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "2-9-3-1",
                                prompt: "What other security measures does BitNasdaq take?",
                                answer: "BitNasdaq deploys security measures like strong Account Password, strong Funds Password, 2-Factor Authentication, strong encryption, and the AML Policy, to protect any fraudulent activities on the exchange.",
                                children: []
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-9-3-2",
                                prompt: "Where can I complete the KYC process on BitNasdaq?",
                                answer: "Sign up on the BitNasdaq exchange, log in your profile, and navigate to the account dashboard. In the account dashboard, navigate to the Identity Authentication tab. In this there is an option available for completing the KYC of the account.",
                                children: []
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-9-3-3",
                                prompt: "What are the requirement for KYC on BitNasdaq?",
                                answer: "The requirements for KYC on BitNasdaq are simple:<ul><li>Valid phone number</li><li>Personal information like DOB</li><li>Valid government issued ID</li><li>Facial recognition</li></ul>",
                                children: []
                            },
                            {
                                id: "2-9-3-4",
                                prompt: "Does BitNasdaq approve the KYC?",
                                answer: "Yes, BitNasdaq approves the KYC. Once requirements have been approved by the team of BitNasdaq, a user’s KYC will be approved.",
                                children: []
                            },
                        ]
                    },
                    {
                        id: "2-9-4",
                        prompt: "How easy is P2P Trading Account Setup?",
                        answer: "Setting up your P2P Trading Account is very easy and simple on the BitNasdaq exchange. All users have to do is signup on the BitNasdaq exchange and setup their BitNasdaq trading account. Once the BitNasdaq account is created and setup, the P2P Trading account is automatically setup.",
                        children: []
                    }
                ],
            },
        ],
    },
    {
        id: "3",
        prompt: "Spot Trading",

        answer: "For Spot Trading, select the option that specifies the category of your query.",
        children: [
            {
                id: "3-1",
                prompt: "About Spot Trading",
                answer: "Spot Trading on BitNasdaq is a simple trade made available for all users. Users have the option to select from different trading pairs on BitNasdaq, as well as choose different trading types. The BitNasdaq trading interface is a very intuitive and easy-to-understand for all its users. Please choose the question you would like to get answered.",
                children: [
                    {
                        id: "3-1-1",
                        prompt: "What is Spot Trading?",
                        answer: "Spot Trading is the type of cryptocurrency trade where users buy and sell their assets instantly on the exchange. Spot Trading is the type where orders are paced and executed instantly. There are no interest rate or margin rate in Spot Trading.",
                        children: [],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "3-1-2",
                        prompt: "What is the difference between Spot and Margin Trading?",
                        answer: "Spot Trading is the trade, buying, and selling of cryptocurrency on the spot and with the updated prices that are present in the market. Whereas, in Margin Trading the user takes a certain loan from the exchange which they are using for trading. This loan is called the leverage in Margin Trade.",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "3-1-2-1",
                                prompt: "Which trade is called Spot Trade?",
                                answer: "Spot Trading is the process of buying and selling cryptocurrencies at the current market price. It is the most common type of trading in the crypto market, and it is done on Spot Markets. Spot Markets are where traders buy and sell assets for immediate delivery.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "3-1-2-2",
                                prompt: "Which trade is called Margin Trade?",
                                answer: "Margin Trading involves using borrowed funds to finance trade, allowing traders to open positions without paying the full amount from their own funds. These borrowed funds are called the leverage. Margin Trading is the where traders utilize leverage.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "3-1-3",
                        prompt: "How does Spot Trading differ from other trading methods?",
                        answer: "Spot Trading is the type of crypto trading where assets are bought or sold immediately. It is referred to as “Spot” because transactions are settled “on the spot”, meaning they occur in real-time without any delay. Other trading methods like Margin Trading, Futures Trading, or Options employ leverage, hedge positions, or take advantage of specific market conditions.",
                        children: [],
                    },
                    {
                        id: "3-1-4",
                        prompt: "What are the strategic differences between Spot Trading & Margin Trading?",
                        answer: "Spot Trading and Margin Trading are two distinct trading strategies that differ in their execution and risk management approaches. Here are the key strategic differences between Spot Trading and Margin Trading: <ul><li>Execution Mechanism</li><li>Use of Leverage</li><li>Risk and Reward Profile</li><li>Funding Cost</li><li>Holding Period</li></ul>",
                        children: [
                            {
                                id: "3-1-3-1",
                                prompt: "What are the different leverages in Spot and Margin Trade?",
                                answer: "Spot Trading does not have any leverage at all, whereas in Margin Trading traders can leverage as big as they desire for completing their trades.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                            {
                                id: "3-1-3-2",
                                prompt: "Which one should I choose, Spot or Margin?",
                                answer: "It's important to note that both Spot Trading and Margin Trading have their advantages and risks. The choice between the two depends on a trader's risk tolerance, investment goals, available capital, and understanding of the market dynamics.",
                                children: [],
                            },
                        ],
                    }
                ],
            },
            {
                id: "3-2",
                prompt: "Spot Wallet",
                answer: "",
                children: [],
            },
            {
                id: "3-3",
                prompt: "Spot Trading",
                answer: "",
                children: [],
            },
            {
                id: "3-4",
                prompt: "Spot Market",
                answer: "",
                children: [],
            },
            {
                id: "3-5",
                prompt: "Spot Interface",
                answer: "",
                children: [],
            },
            {
                id: "3-6",
                prompt: "Spot Limit Orders",
                answer: "",
                children: [],
            },
            {
                id: "3-7",
                prompt: "Spot Market Orders",
                answer: "",
                children: [],
            },
            {
                id: "3-8",
                prompt: "Spot Trigger Orders",
                answer: "",
                children: [],
            },
        ],
    },
    {
        id: "4",
        prompt: "Margin Trading",

        answer: "",
        children: [],
    },
    {
        id: "5",
        prompt: "Future Contracts",

        answer: "",
        children: [],
    },
    {
        id: "6",
        prompt: "Copy Trading",

        answer: "",
        children: [],
    },
    {
        id: "7",
        prompt: "Financial Staking",

        answer: "",
        children: [],
    },
    {
        id: "8",
        prompt: "Account Security",

        answer: "",
        children: [],
    },
    {
        id: "9",
        prompt: "Identity Authentication",

        answer: "",
        children: [],
    },
    {
        id: "10",
        prompt: "Affiliate Program",

        answer: "",
        children: [],
    },
    {
        id: "11",
        prompt: "Referral Program",

        answer: "",
        children: [],
    },
    {
        id: "12",
        prompt: "Reward Hub",

        answer: "",
        children: [],
    },
    {
        id: "13",
        prompt: "Converter Calculator",

        answer: "",
        children: [],
    },
    {
        id: "14",
        prompt: "Trading Bots",

        answer: "",
        children: [],
    },
    {
        id: "15",
        prompt: "VIP And Fee Plan",

        answer: "",
        children: [],
    },
    {
        id: "16",
        prompt: "Partner Program",

        answer: "",
        children: [],
    },
    {
        id: "17",
        prompt: "Mock Trading",

        answer: "",
        children: [],
    },
    {
        id: "18",
        prompt: "bRound",

        answer: "",
        children: [],
    },
    {
        id: "19",
        prompt: "Investment Plan",

        answer: "",
        children: [],
    },
    {
        id: "20",
        prompt: "General Questions",

        answer: "",
        children: [],
    },
];
